Average calculates the average of a specific column throughout the table, while
Average X calculates the average of a personalized expression evaluated row per row in a
table and then take the average of these results. A personalized expression is a written formula
In Dax. A measure is a personalized expression. To understand the difference well, let's see an example.
to create the new AGEGEGE measure in the Olympic Events table. Let's click on New Measure and
We name him as we said that he is Age avege and this will be the same as average x.aquí
It is of the values ​​that are in each row for the different games, that is, for each of
The Olympic Games. Then that means the values ​​of Games, we close parentheses, coma and
We are going to calculate, calculate for each of those games the average of the age colon.
And we close parentheses and enter.aca we have our measure Age avege.Average x allows us to get the
average column but taking into account blocks of rows, in this case the Olympic Games,
That is, the different Olympics. In the visualization module we will open a page,
We are going to call it X and we will create a matrix and we locate Games in Rows
And the new measure in Values, Age average in Values.
And so we can see the average age in each of the Olympics and the average age in
all the games that have been 25.8 years. Let's see the difference with average, we will go to
Transform Data, that is, in Power Query and we are going to select our Olimpic Events dataset
And we are going to click on the header of the AGE variable, we verify that the type of
data is an integer number, effectively has the Whole Number icon and we will locate the
Number module column at the top, being in transform and here is Number column and we are going
to click on the statistical functions to locate average.power query shows us the result,
This is the average age of all athletes who have competed in all the Olympics of the
History until 2016, but with average we cannot know the average age for each of the
Olympic games, as we see the value is different because this is an average
AGE column numbers, with average X the average age of age averages is calculated
of each Olympiad.In the next class we will see the Rank X function, see you