And after they have corrupted all the Jews, they will also reach Impedles to all the infidels.
As someone who spent 32 years in Shevka, there is no difference between the Hametz and the Volselin authority, those are prey and those are waste.
If I don't include a diskette that will do it immediately, we are not in the same situation as the sixth of October.
Today we are in danger, which is not an existential danger.
Who was waiting for me? More than 30 years in Shevak, who is in charge of investigations in Shevuk and who had the opportunity to personally investigate the likes of Sinuar and other villains no less than him.
After your extensive experience, if I had to ask you, what would you like the public to know about organizations and these people in one sentence?
what do you think? We do not know about them and it is right that we know about them.
This is a very cruel Nazi organization.
This organization actually wants and has always wanted to kill Jews, kill Jews.
As Yesinuar himself told me more than once?
did you feel
I have personally been questioned several times that his wet dream is to enter Israel with the Nokba units and kill Jews wherever they are.
And after they have corrupted all the Jews, they will also reach Impedles to all the infidels.
In 1989, I was waiting for me, I created all of Hamas.
The entire military faction of Hamas, 520 people, I narrowed down.
Among them, Ahmed Yassi, at Achsha, Deniza Rabodel, Larnetisi, Mahmoud, Zohar, everyone you can think of, I'm worried.
And of course also Yahs, Inuar, Berv Himushta, Marvin Naisa, all of them were the Tsurim.
And when I met with Rabin, in a personal meeting, after the investigation, when he was interested, I told him Mr. Prime Minister.
This organization, the Nazi organization, is extremely dangerous against Israel, we must destroy it when it is small,
Oh, we have to release restraints on the helo.
It was in 1989.
Since then I have made a number of replacement entitlements,
When the first among them was Jibril, in 1985 1500 terrorists were killed.
We ate it big.
When Rabin deported 400 people to Lebanon, 100 to Hamas, with a lot of casualties,
The prosecution objected to defend his position.
And then he had to return them all after a while,
to Israel, when there was already a period of its name, they trained and absorbed its name,
All kinds of opinions after.
Rabin was humiliated, Rabin was greatly humiliated by the prosecution.
and yet...
You don't see Bin Shatirva representing him in a garment.
Still.
And yet, the acquaintance of the late Haim Berashim Tzerk Rabin,
and the familiarity that is not with Hamas,
They later led him to no less dubious concessions.
Look, there were a number of shady deals,
As I said the first was Gabriel,
Then there was Sharon's win with a thousand and one,
And for the three bodies in Tenenbarb.
And before I have to say,
All of Oslo, just a week ago,
A Palestinian policeman shoots with a weapon provided by the IDF.
Come on, I just want to tell you, I,
As someone who spent 32 years in Shevc,
There is no difference between Hamas and the Palestinian Authority.
Those, Trepa and those for Bella.
I was at Shev K in a senior position,
But I was never afraid to speak my mind,
Even in front of them, degrees of freedom,
Other network heads, without remembering names,
A lot of mistakes were made.
People followed politics.
People went to help one prime minister or another,
only politically,
Only you, in my opinion, people are Shebek people.
Shebak people.
Not politicians.
I said I didn't mention that it was donated,
They are very simple to please prime ministers
from a certain area,
They just followed them.
And so many steps that caused us to make terrible mistakes sometimes.
I'll give you an example.
Because when I first wanted to do but from design,
Someone told me,
I'm not going to make a mess of Rabin.
If I have to simplify the things you say,
You say that inside the Shev as Warsaw,
There are political considerations.
Unfortunately yes.
Look, we have
kind of method,
that each
in places, not only in the police,
Even in the crowd, also in the sky everywhere,
who want to pass the period of silence.
Everyone wants to move forward.
You are his shift.
You keep his watch quietly.
Which is a terrible trait for daddies.
These concepts have changed,
Both military personnel and politicians.
For example, you see,
When you hear a certain sentence,
that I hear rose in joy,
which says that it must be released
kidnapped at any cost,
including reaching the 60 October limits,
This is the dropout concept.
He didn't change the diskette.
I don't have any battery on the cell phones
were for October,
And there were huge cells.
There was an unprecedented failure.
Of course I'm angry.
And I'm angry at all those people
They vacated these cells.
Even though they are currently doing a good job,
and they continue,
and they fight,
And they are Hebrew people.
And some of them I also know personally.
They are really Hebrew people.
But the doubts they made
will not be forgiven,
She must never be forgiven.
We must all unite
in the fight against
Or this foreigner of the nation.
And if we don't do it,
He will stand up again,
He will rebuild himself,
And we will see another such range,
in other places.
the authority,
We have to reckon
with all the sayings,
said by the heads of the Authority
Right after this war.
They said hail, Yuba TV everywhere,
to be reached in additional settlements,
and cook
It is necessary to make an account with them.
Don't dwell on it.
do not hesitate,
We must reckon with them.
We must not leave this issue
of payments to witnesses,
To the families who are witnesses.
This topic must be deleted from the world.
what is mine important,
let there be unity,
let there be a fight,
She bows to anyone who wants to
to touch us,
If it is in Judah and Shimron,
Baba and Adi also Buzzer.
We all owe these things
Remember, whoever I don't curse
diskette that will do this immediately,
We are not in the same situation
of the sixth of October.
We are in danger today.
that even existential danger.
And if we don't do it,
It will come upon us as Boomer-ang.
what a request
the theme of the hijabs,
And the most painful subject we have
in the defense of Israel.
This should be an important goal
Bring them all back. but,
I'm one of those who say no at all costs.
if it depends,
This is who we are as a country,
We can't compromise the image
ours as a country.
We will have to
release them by other means.
no way,
And of course not at your expense
the surrounding settlements,
and not at the expense of
Then Amdala punched into the strip.
We will not be given to Hamas
to exist forever.
Must conquer and destroy
all his abilities,
take care of that,
When they are no longer in power, never.