And after slaughtering all the Jews they will also reach Infidels
To all the infidels
Because the one who was in Shebak for 32 years
There is no difference between Hamas and the Palestinian Authority
These are prey and these are waste
Whoever does not pull out a diskette will do so immediately
We are not in the same situation as the Friday of October
Today we are in danger, even existential danger
Who was waiting for me?
Over 30 years in Shebak
The person in charge of investigations in Shebak
And those who got to investigate personally
You are Yahya Sinwar
And more are allowed no less than him
After your experience tonight
should i have asked you
What would you like the public to know about these organizations and people in one sentence?
what do you think?
We don't know about them and it's right that we know about them
You see, this is a very cruel Nazi organization
this organization
actually want to
And always wanted to
kill jews
Jews swim
Long live Sinuar himself told me more than once
How personally?
I am personally under investigation
Number of times
that his wet dream
It is to enter Israel
with the piercing units
of sorts and to swim Jews
As they
After they corrupted all the Jews
They will also come to Infadels
To all the infidels
in 1989
I'm waiting for me
I arrested all of Hamas
The entire military faction of Hamas
520 people
I stopped
Among them are only Madiasi, Selah, Shacha, Denizhara and Rodel, Larnetsi
Mahmoud, Zohar
Everyone you just think
I stopped
And of course, long live the sinewer
And when I met with Rabin
in a personal meeting after
The investigation when he was interested
I told him Mr. Prime Minister
This organization is a Nazi organization
Extremely dangerous for the State of Israel
We must destroy him
When he is small, woe to us
If we release these restraints
It was in 89
since
A number were made
Exchange transactions
When the first between them was a deal
Jibril in 1985
release
1500 terrorists
We ate it big
When Rabin removed 400 people
to Lebanon from Hamas
And very much the organizations of the attorney's office
She refused to defend his position
Then he was forced some time later
Return them all to Israel
When they had already been there for a while
We trained and soaked there
All kinds of other opinions
Rabin was humiliated in the meeting
It was great by the prosecution
and yet
Dori Bini she added
to represent him in Bagetz
And still your acquaintance
With the late Prime Minister Yzerek Rabin
and his acquaintance with Hamas
They led him further
No less dubious transactions
Look there were a number of shady deals
Like I said first
There was Jibril
Then there was Sharon's deal
with a thousand and some
The three bodies
And before that it should be said
All of Oslo just a week ago
Palestinian policeman
shoots with a weapon
provided by the army
Come on, I just want to tell you
I am like someone who spent 32 years in Shevak
There is no difference between Hamas
and the Palestinian Authority
These are prey and these are waste
I was in a trap
in a senior position
I was afraid to express my opinion
Even in front of those degrees freedoms
Shebak chiefs and others
without mentioning names
A lot of mistakes
people went
After politics
people went to
to help one or another prime minister
Only politically
promote themselves
Shebak people
I said I wouldn't mention names to them
They are very simple
to please
Prime ministers
from a certain area
They just followed them
and took steps that made us
for blunders
sometimes
I will give you an example
When I first wanted to stop her
You are Ahmed Yassin
Someone told me
I'm not going to make a mess for the Rebbe
If I have to simplify the things you say
which is inside the hole
and rested
There are political considerations
Unfortunately yes
Look we have
sex
method
every one
In many places, not only in the police
Both in joy and in heaven
Wherever you want to move
the period of silence
Everyone wants to pass a term
his shift
which is a lousy feature
In my opinion
The concept has not changed
Also military personnel and politicians
When you hear a certain sentence
I hear Alosh in joy
who says
to be released
Kidnapped at any cost
Including withdrawal to the borders of October 6
And the concept remained
He didn't sleep on the diskette
I don't have any savings
About the disappointments that were for October
And there were huge elephants
There was an unprecedented failure
Of course I'm angry
And I'm angry at all those people
These cellulosic swamps
Even though they currently do
Good job and they keep going
and fight
They are brilliant people
And some of them I also know personally
They are really brilliant people
But the doubts they made
They will not steal
Guaranteed forever
We must all unite
in the fight against
The enemy reclaims the nation
And if we don't do it
He will get back on his feet
He will rebuild himself
And we will see more
such a range
in other places
We must take the authority into account
with all the sayings
said by the heads of the Authority immediately after
this war
On the radio, on television
Anywhere to be touched
in additional settlements and to cook
And you have to reckon with them
Don't panic about it, this panic
She is the weakness you talk too much about
We must reckon with them
We can not
Leave this issue of
Payments to martyrs
to the families who testify
This topic must be deleted from the world
What is important to me is that there should be unity
There will be a fight
You are there for anyone who wants it
to touch us
If it is in Judea and Moron, if it is in Lebanon
Certainly also in Gaza
We must have these things
We all remember
Whoever does not pull out a diskette will do so immediately
We are not in the same situation
of the sixth of October
We are in danger today
that even existential danger
And if we don't do it, it will come upon us
like a boomerang
There is no doubt that the subject of the abductees
This is the most painful issue
that we have today in the defense of Israel
This should be an important task
Bring them all back
But I am one of those who claim
Not at any cost
if it depends on it
We are also a country
we can not
to damage our image as a country
We will have to
release them
by other means
No way
not at the expense of
The settlements of Ha'ofet
And not at the expense of him entering
Amla followed him into a strip
We will not be given to Hamas
to exist forever
Must conquer and destroy
all his abilities
and make sure they are no more
In power, never