average calculates the average of a specific column across the entire table, while
average x calculates the average of a custom expression evaluated row by row in a
table and then take the average of those results. A custom expression is a formula written
in DAX.A measure is a custom expression.To understand the difference well, let's look at an example.Let's go
to create the new age average measure in the Olympic events table. We click on new measure and
We name the measure that we said is age average and this will be equal to average x.Here
is the values ​​that are in each row for the different games, that is, for each of
the Olympic games. So that means the values ​​of games, we close parentheses, comma and
We are going to calculate, calculate for each of those games the average of the age column.
And we close parentheses and enter.Here we have our age average.Average x measurement allows us to get the
average of the column but taking into account blocks of rows, in this case the Olympic games,
that is, the different Olympics. In the visualization module we are going to open a page,
We are going to call it x and we are going to create a matrix and place games in rows
and the new measure in values, age average in values.
And so we can see the average age in each of the Olympics and the average age in
all the games it has been 25.8 years. Let's see the difference with average, we are going to go to
transform data, that is, in power query and we are going to select our olímpic events dataset
and we are going to click on the header of the age variable, we verify that the type of
data is an integer, it actually has the whole number icon and we are going to locate the
module number column at the top, being in transform and here is number column and let's go
to click on the statistical functions to locate average.Power query shows us the result,
This is the average age of all the athletes who have competed in all the Olympic Games of the
history until 2016, but with average we cannot know the average age for each of the
Olympic games, as we see the value is different because this is a single average of all the
numbers in the age column, with average x the average of the age averages is calculated
of each Olympics. In the next class we will see the rank x function, see you