The relationships between the number of boxes and time are different. We see that although
we have the same regression line, we have four different data behaviors.
What we just saw is a very powerful concept in statistics called the Anscom quartet, which
shows us the importance of seeing the shape of the data, the relationships between the variables,
and it is important in data storytelling because the shape of the data helps us find the context
of the story that we are going to tell. After seeing the shape of the data and finding
relationships, the storyteller will identify with one of those relationships and will decide
to tell the story from that angle, giving prominence to certain variables.
And when we find that angle, from where we will tell the story, we will also discover
the feeling that it generates and that we are going to generate in the audience. We want that
During the story that we are going to tell, the audience feels happy, surprised, afraid,
with rage, embarrassed or empowered, with desire to conquer the world. First we must discover
how we feel to replicate that feeling. First we must discover how we feel to replicate
the feeling.